<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TestGit</string>

    <string name="nome">name: %1$s</string>
    <string name="idioma">language: %1$s</string>
    <string name="titulo">Title</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_navigation">MainNavigationActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_favorite">Favorites</string>
    <string name="title_about">About</string>

    <string name="sobre">
         <![CDATA[
        <h1>What is git?</h1>
        <p align="justify">
        Git is a file version control system. Through them we can develop projects in which several people can contribute simultaneously in the same, editing and creating new files and allowing them to exist without the risk of their changes being overwritten.
        </p>
        <p align="justify">

        If there is no version system, imagine the chaos between two people opening the same file at the same time. One of the applications of git is precisely this, allowing a file to be edited at the same time by different people. As complex as that is, he tries to keep everything in order to avoid problems for us developers.
        </p>
        <p align="justify">
        Another important factor of git (and this is one of its differences in relation to svn - if you know it) is the possibility to create, at any moment, several snapshots of your project, or what we call more "nerdmenete", branch. Suppose your project is an html site, and you want to create a new section in your HTML code, but at that point you do not want these changes to be available to anyone else, just for you. That is, you want to change the project (including multiple files in it), but you still do not want this to be treated as "official" to other people, so you create a branch (like a mirror copy) , until you hit all the details of it. After that, you can merge back from your branch to the original project. You see, if all this you read only helped to confuse you more - take a deep breath - and move on. With examples everything gets better.
        </p>
        <h2>What is github?</h2>
        <p align="justify">
        Github is a web service that offers several extra features applied to git. In short, you can use github for free to host your personal projects. In addition, almost all open source development projects / frameworks / libraries are in github, and you can follow them through new versions, contribute bugs or even send code and patches. If you are a developer and do not have github yet, you are late and this is the time to chase after the loss.
        </p>
        ]]>

    </string>



    <string name="txt_fechar">Close</string>
    <string name="nenhuma_informacao_localizada">No localized information</string>
    <string name="git_title">GitHub Test</string>
    <string name="subtittle_sobre">About</string>
    <string name="subtittle_favoritos">Favorites</string>
    <string name="subtittle_home">Home</string>


</resources>
